Okay, so we have already discussed perfect competition in the imperfect competition of Param.
So, imperfect competition is the first type of Marcus Bhaktaris, monopolistic competition, monopolistic
competition.
So, monopolistic competition is the key to the thing that we wrote in the first word,
differentiated product.
By the way, these sellers have become a product,
but suppose they are so poor, they are so poor, they are differentiated.
Like you have loves, you have a brand like Pierce,
so in the brand I love it, they are a different ad, okay?
Poor product and differentiated, it can be the color, it can be the design, it can be the ingredients, can be anything.
So, in the product category,
are there are pros, firms, elements, other differentiated,
they are the type of Marcus structure, monopolistic competition.
So, on the other hand, what happens when you have differentiated product,
advertisements, promotions, and all of the decor, all of them, okay?
But, shape, perfect competition, you know, perfect competition,
all of them are selling the same product.
So, there is not much scope for advertisement or anything,
but in monopolistic competition, you know, are a scope and they are selling,
differentiated products, and products have closed substitutes, okay?
Substitutes and the perfect competition for that is perfect,
but she is a very pro-sattler of substitutes,
and if one of the firm increases the price,
the Luxembourger increase the price increase either you know Luxembourger,
or the Neula Ver is open to a level, what you think is more similar to Luxembourger,
so parking limit or can demand here.
So, that means they have closed substitutes.
Incoming to the features, just like perfect competition, every day in large number of buyers
and sellers at the purchase sellers and companies compared to perfect competition, it is kind of
less. Then you have product differentiation which I already mentioned, free number of entry and
Panda negativity firms can enter an exit, another special solution.