Let's talk about Python. What is it? How does it work and how you can get started today?
All of that and more in two minutes. Start the timer.
Python is a prevalent general purpose programming language often used from machine learning
in data analysis. Python was created by Guido Van Rossum and was first released on February 20, 1991.
This language is so influential that in 1999 the Zenfiton was released, which is a guiding
set of principles for using Python in the upmost Mr. Miyagi way. There are numerous reasons
why this language is hotter than the backstreet boys were in 1997. The first being that Python is
very readable, like it's state-to-ness Zenfiton. Simple is better than complex, and that's
exactly what the language mirrors. Python can also handle a multitude of different jobs,
for machine learning, to data, analytics, web development, testing, and so on.
There is no need to debate how great this language is, but how can we use it? You can download
Python on the official getting started with Python page. Once downloaded, creating a file with Python
is as easy as naming the file and ending it with .py. These files are also referred to as modules.
Then all you need to do is print hello world, and there you go. You can practice all your
friends that you are the next Bill Gates. You have probably heard of interpreted versus compiled,
right? Well, Python is an interpreted language, which means the source code is converted into
that is then executed by the Python virtual machine. This equates to Python being extremely
fast to develop, but not so fast during the execution step, since the code is not directly
compiled and executed. But why should we learn Python? Probably the most important answer to that
is just how beginner friendly the language is. If you're brain new to web development,
my recommendation is either learned Python or JavaScript. You can't go wrong with either.
As we mentioned before, Python is also extremely versatile. You can do so many different tasks
with just one language. Lastly, Python developers are extremely in demand. There are 36,000
job postings on zippercouter at this current moment for entry-level Python developers.
If you want to learn Python and fully master one of the most relevant languages in the world
of development, check out zero to masteries complete Python developer bootcamp course.
Will you go from beginner to expert?